justplug.it 2013-09-27

# JustPlugIt | Privacy Policy

This website (the "Site") and the services/products/software provided herein (the " **Services** "), as defined below, is made available to you by Standart LLC ("Standart"). In this Privacy Policy we explain the type of information we collect through our Site, and Services, and what we do with such information.

This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms and conditions available at:

Terms of service

If you choose to enter our Site and use our Services you will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms: "the company", "we" and "us" refer to Standart LLC. or any successor or assign of Standart LLC.

## Privacy and use of information

Standart' personal information practices are governed by this Privacy Policy. Please review it before making any use of our Site and Services. 

By using the Services you also agree to this privacy statement. You acknowledge that (a) we cannot ensure the security or privacy of information you provide through the Internet and your email messages, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such information by other parties; (b) we are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the personal information you provide to others through the service; and (c) we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of messages sent by other users of the service, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any communications you may receive from other users. We cannot guarantee, and assume no responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the information provided by other users of the service.

You may be asked to provide us, during the registration process and use of the Service, with two types of information; personal information such as name, address, e-mail address and e-mails, and any other personal information, if required.

When you use the Service and/or log on to the Site, we may collect and receive your browser information, including IP address, "cookies" information [email name IP address cookie].

We may provide your personal information to third parties since our Service is also supplied by third parties. Please note that these third parties may have a different privacy policy.

As specified above, we may collect certain information about you and your web usage, which may be shared with third parties and used for advertising. NOTE: OUR SOFTWARE AND OTHER SERVICES COLLECT AND STORES INFORMATION CONCERNING YOUR ACTIVITY ON THE WEB, SUCH AS YOUR IP ADDRESS. IN SOME CASES, INFORMATION COLLECTED BY OUR SERVICES MAY BE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AND IN SOME CASES INFORMATION (INCLUDING INFORMATION FROM OR ABOUT PAGES OF SOCIAL MEDIA WEBSITES YOU VISIT) MAY BE USED OR SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR PURPOSES OF DISPLAYING TARGETED ADVERTISEMENTS PROMOTIONAL AND MARKETING MATERIAL TO YOU.

We may also release your information when we believe that such release is necessary in order to: (a) protect or defend any of our legal rights (including enforcement of agreements that we have interest in) or property, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors; (b) comply with applicable law, legal process or enforce our site policies. (c) Protect the safety and security of users of our Site and any of our Services or members of the public; or (d) protect against fraud or carry out our risk management procedures.

## Unsolicited Submission Policy

Standart does not accept, by any means of transmission, any unsolicited submissions, in any form whatsoever including, without limitation, any marketing, advertising and/or creative suggestions, scripts, lyrics, jingles, product samples, prototypes, movies and/or games (hereinafter referred to as "Submissions"). If you elect to forward to us any such Submission, then by doing so, you acknowledge that said Submission has not been requested by us and that (1) we are not liable for any use, disclosure, or return to you of your Submission, (2) no confidential relationship is established or is to be implied in any way from our receipt of the Submission and any statement to the contrary with your Submission shall not alter this condition, (3) you understand that you will not be entitled to any compensation from us based upon your Submission, (4) the receipt of your Submission shall not constitute a waiver by us of our rights to contest the validity of any copyright, or other intellectual property rights that you may now or hereafter claim for the Submission, and (5) any previously, concurrently or subsequently submitted materials relating to this Submission shall be considered to have been submitted in accordance with these conditions.

## Modifications

Standart LLC. reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Such modifications shall be in full force and effect immediately upon publication. Notification of changes in this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Service/ Site (as defined in the Terms and Conditions) or sent via electronic mail, as we may determine in our sole discretion. If you do not agree to any modifications, you should terminate your use of the service/software immediately upon the publications of such change. Your continued use of the service/software now, or following the posting of notice of any changes in this Privacy Policy, will constitute a binding acceptance by you of this Privacy Policy, or any subsequent modifications.

## Disclosure and communication

We reserve the right to send electronic mail to you, for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to the service, or of any service's related products and services. We reserve the right to disclose information about your usage of the service and demographics in forms that do not reveal your personal identity.

## "RSS" Feeds

RSS feeds may be provided as a quick and easy way for you to distribute information from the web site or from your online account. RSS feeds are accessible through an XML-based URL that can be accessed with an RSS reader of your choice. You consent that the information in the feeds will be transferred to the location in which you enable the RSS feed. Standart will not pass any personally identifiable information in your feed. However, your use of an RSS feed may cause personally identifiable information that is associated with the RSS feed to be associated with you. You acknowledge that your use of an RSS feed and any personally identifiable information associated with it is at your sole discretion and risk.

Use of the service's RSS feeds is for non-commercial, personal use and whether or not you use an RSS feed is entirely at your discretion. You may not modify the RSS feeds. If an RSS feed contains an attribution to the service, you may not remove the attribution. Standart provides no warranty regarding its RSS feeds and reserves the right to terminate or modify the feeds at any time without notice. Standart is not responsible for any loss or damage incurred by you or anyone else due to your use of an RSS feed.

## Language

You agree that this Privacy Policy, the Site and the Service and all communications with Standart shall be in the English language.

## Entire Agreement

You agree that this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and Standart with respect to your use of this Site and the Service and supersede all previous agreements, understandings and representations relating thereto.
